naaleads.com 2008-04-15

# National Agents Alliance Corporate : Our Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy  
  
We at National Agents Alliance are firmly committed to maintaining the privacy of every visitor to our website. Please notice that we ask only the briefest of information in order to speak to you about personal matters in person and privately.  
  
Individual User Information  
  
All individually identifiable visitor information we gather, including e-mail addresses, will not be released or disclosed to any third parties without the visitor's prior consent. This information will be used solely by National Agents Alliance and/or it's authorized agents. The information you provide will only be used to determine which if any products we have might be of benefit to you. Should you decide to move forward, we will only forward personal information to the respective insurance company after you have approved and signed the application.  
  
Site Statistics  
  
National Agents Alliance gathers site usage information, or statistics, from all visitors. This information includes such data as number of visitors, sessions and page views, length of visits, pages visited and other such information. This data is only used in the aggregate, however, to help determine general usage patterns which will allow us to continually fine-tune our website. This statistical information may be made public at our discretion. None of this data contains any personal information or information that can be traced back to any specific visitor.  
  
Cookies  
  
Cookies are tiny bits of information placed by a website on a visitors personal computer. They help track a visitor's session while online. Although in general our website does not utilize cookies, certain aspects of our website may not function without them. Cookies are not related to any personally identifiable information and are not used to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent in a Cookie.

Many browsers are set to accept Cookies. You may prefer to set your browser to refuse Cookies. Please be aware that some areas of our website will not function properly if you do so. All Cookies will expire once a visitor leaves our website.

Click here to learn more about [cookies](http://cookiecentral.com/faq/).  
  
Information We Disclose  
  
We do not disclose any nonpublic personal information about our customers or former customers to anyone, except as permitted or required by law.  
  
Security And Confidentiality of Customer Information  
  
We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to guard all nonpublic personal information. We restrict access to personal information about our customers to those employees or affiliates who require the information to provide products and services.  
  
External Links  
  
National Agents Alliance provides links to other websites not directly under the control of NAA or its affiliates. We provide them to our website visitors so that they may become more fully informed about our products and industry. NAA is not responsible for the privacy policies maintained on those sites and we encourage our users to read the privacy policies of all websites they visit.  
  
Changes To This Statement  
  
Our Privacy Policy is subject to change without notice. Any changes will be posted on this page before they become effective.  
  
Disclaimer  
  
We do our best to ensure that any information contained on this website is correct. However, we cannot be responsible for the accuracy of this information. If you find that any link or information we have provided is in any way not acceptable, has been changed or is no longer working, please contact us and let us know.

Thank you for visiting our website. Please come back soon.
